Thank you for watching!
I'm going to the rehearsal.
I'll do my best.
It's the last day of the Japanese tour.
The rehearsal is over.
Wow, it's beautiful.
Wow, it's so big.
The rehearsal is over.
Thank you for your cooperation.
The last day of the Japanese tour.
We are MIRACLE!
Thank you for your support!
I love you
It's okay.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy to see the lights are
moving.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy that all the Boy Scouts
are waving their hands.
And...
We want to introduce other dance so.
We'll be delivering your heartbeat to
everyone!
We will!
What is it?
This is amongamon.
We love affections.
Is it true?
one of these?
Thank you for watching so far. We'll
come back with more delicious videos :)
Live on...
I'm about to burst, I can't hold it
anymore
I can't help it, I can't help it
Thank you for your hard work.
It was fun.
It was new.
We finished the rehearsal.
We finished.
I'm going to introduce myself.
What are you doing?
It's starting!
I'm nervous, unlike usual.
It's a strange feeling.
I'm nervous.
I'll do my best.
How do you do it?
I'm nervous.
At sea.
Q. This event is very important to you?
Also, please register and like.
Buy a baklak and buy burdock gifts
Sumi-chan wielding an operatvasive roll
The tension in the audience runs high
Sumi Joy's new song
How will it play out?
Regulated playground
Sumi goes back from pretty high
To not be recorded
surveilling handmadefficial
TV-san, today is a party!
Tumor, tumor, tumor, the strongest!
Hello, hello to the sad truth!
It doesn't matter what you say
The symptoms that can't be cured
Tumor, tumor, tumor, the strongest!
Hello, hello to the possibilities of
humanity!
The future that you want to see is now
Happy new day!
Go! Go! Tumor! Go! Go! Tumor!
Let's run, Tumor!
Let's grow everyday
We're 6th place!
Thank you for watching!
Today we were invited to Join Jubilee's
grand event
We were happy that the official
supporters are present
And we did the Live
That event isn't our usual schedule
It was feeling fresh
I totally enjoyed their looking at us
Thank you!
We were able to do it!
Thank you so much!
We will do our best to make this event
more fun!
Thank you for this precious
opportunity!
It was fun!
Jumping is the best!
The best!